Joseph Carré

Website: <u>www.joecarre.co.uk</u> **Email:** carre.joe3@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/carrejoe3 **Address:** Flat 5,

5 Windsor Road,

Ealing,

London W5 3UL

Personal Summary:

07578103110

I am a developer based in Ealing Broadway that has experience with a wide variety of languages, including over three years professional experience creating responsive web and mobile applications. More specifically, I have used the following:

-HTMI

Phone:

- -CSS
- -SCSS
- -Javascript
- -D3.is
- -Jquery/Jquery mobile
- -PHP
- -SQL
- -XML
- -Xpath
- -C#
- -Bootstrap
- -Git
- -TFS
- -Cordova/Phonegap
- -Wordpress

In my current role, I have been tasked with upgrading the existing codebase from jQuery to Vue.js, which has given me the opportunity to learn how to create applications with more modern frameworks.

I also have two years experience designing user interfaces using tools such as InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator and most recently Adobe XD.

I have worked in both large and small organisations, using both agile and waterfall methodologies. I have been involved in every part of a products development life cycle, from the planning stage, initial design and prototyping stages, development stages, testing and finally maintenance and updates, and therefore have a very good understanding of what a products development life cycle entails.

I would love the opportunity to contribute to an organisation that truly values creativity and is changing the world for the better. Please find further information about myself, as well as examples of previous work on my portfolio website:

www.joecarre.co.uk

Relevant Experience:

Front End Developer, Accession Healthcare, October 2018 - Present

• I have been developing iPad applications for international pharmaceutical companies. This involves creating designs using InDesign, Illustrator and Photoshop, then building said applications using Xcode, Phonegap, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, SQL, PHP, Bootstrap and Sass.

Front End Developer, RFA Advertising and Marketing, October 2017 – October 2018

 This role involves creating promotional material for international pharmaceutical companies, including emails, websites and iPad presentations. Projects are designed with Adobe Indesign, Photoshop and Illustrator, then marked up in VS code/Sublime/Dreamweaver using HTML, CSS, Javascript and Jquery, utilising Github as source control.

Graduate Developer, Focus Solutions, July 2016 - October 2017

• I worked in the product team, utilising Agile methodologies to create new products according to requirements from Standard Life. This involved using Javascript, HTML, CSS, Jquery, C#, SQL, XML and Xpath.

Programmer, Learning Support Service, November 2014 – March 2015

• I produced an interactive flash game for their website. This would be used by the clients disabled students when learning the alphabet.

Employment:

Head of Production, Pure FM, May 2014 – March 2015

- I was elected to become a part of the committee as the head of production for the University of Portsmouth's student radio station.
- I produced new jingles, power intros as well as other audio that the station required.

Founder Substitute Events, March 2014 – January 2015

- I founded an events company in Portsmouth in a popular club in the town centre.
- I boosted the events attendance through traditional methods such as flyers and posters as well as online on social media.

Founder House Party Events, March 2013 - August 2013

- I started an events company which ran a successful night in one of the best clubs in Oxford.
- I successfully managed a team of staff dedicated towards promotion as well as running the night itself.

Presenter, Off The Chart Online Radio Show, December 2011- December 2012

- I hosted an online radio show every Saturday from seven until nine pm, playing a broad range of music within the dance genre.
- I also increased listener numbers through online promotion. The station can be found at: http://www.offthechartradio.co.uk/

Music Producer, Club-stream Record Label, June 2013 - Present

- I am signed to an independent Swedish record label based in Gothenburg.
- I have released two E.P's with the label which are available on iTunes, Beatport, Juno and Spotify. I have also produced a remix for another artist on the label which has been released to all major online music stores.

Bartender, The Gate Hangs High, Hook Norton 14th July - September 28th 2013

• This role required me to serve people behind the bar, wait tables, cash up the till after a night shift and also general maintenance of the property.

Bartender- The Chequers Public House, Chipping Norton 27th June 2012 – 10th April 2013

• This job required a huge amount of customer service skills due to the popularity of the establishment and an ability to work quickly in busy periods.

Crew Member - McDonalds Restaurant, Banbury 3rd June – September 2nd 2012

• This required a high degree of interaction and service skills in order to maximise the customer experience and satisfaction overall.

Achievements & Interests:

- Playing guitar
- Music production, DJing and sound engineering
- Squash and tennis

Education:

- University of Portsmouth BSc (Hons) Entertainment Technology 2013 2016
- Chipping Norton Sixth Form 2010 2012
- Chipping Norton School 2007 2010
- Trinity School and Performing Arts College, Newbury 2005 2007

References:

Michelle Mahoney,
The Learning Support Service,
Owner / Proprietor,
0776 9660998
michellemahoney@
thelearningsupportservice.com

Dr Steve Hand, University of Portsmouth, Winston Churchill Ave, Portsmouth. PO1 2UP steve.hand@port.ac.uk